http://www.abateofindiana.org/privacy-policy/

Information about our Organization and Website
ABATE of Indiana, Inc. is based in Bargersville, Indiana with corportae offices in Fort Wayne, Indiana.
Our principal activity
Membership organization
Our privacy policy covers ABATE of Indiana Inc. and its websites
Organization Name: ABATE of Indiana Inc.
Address: PO Box 665 (51 North Baldwin St), Bargersville, Indiana, 46106
Website(s): www.ABATEonline.org, www.ABATEofindiana.org, www.ABATEofindiana.com, www.ABATEproducts.com, www.hoosiermotorcyclist.com
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.
The services and links of our Web sites
Our Web sites do not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. Our Web sites may include links to third party Web service providers.
Automatic Collection of Information
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while applying for membership. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.
Confidentiality / Security
We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:
Primary personal data (such as name and contact details)
Identifiers (such as credit card details)
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
Unauthorised accessImproper use or disclosure
Unauthorised modification
Unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Privacy Compliance
There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.
Privacy Support
If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:
Name/Designation: ABATE of Indiana
Address: ABATE of Indiana, PO Box 665, Bargersville, IN 46106
Phone Number: 800-23-ABATE
Email address: abate@abateonline.org
URL: www.abateonline.org
Copyright © ABATE of Indiana, Inc. 2020 ® All Rights Reserved. |
Privacy Policy
